PERMANENT ADDRESS 3605 Indigo Creek Trail Kennesaw, GA 30144

Janet Chen

770-883-4816 | Jtchen@uga.edu

CURRENT ADDRESS 950 Marietta Street, apt 3317 Atlanta, GA 30318

With over six years of customer service experience and multiple leadership positions, I have the ability to comfortably socialize and understand the unique needs of individuals. I am a fast learner and efficient worker, and my technology knowledge and language fluency will prove useful in modern workplaces.

EDUCATION

Georgia State University, Atlanta, GA

Expected May 2019

Master's in Occupational Therapy, College of Nursing and Health Professionals

The University of Georgia, Athens, GA

May 2017

Bachelor of Science in Health Promotion, College of Public Health

GPA: 3.46/4.00

SKILLS

- Languages: English, Fluently speak Mandarin Chinese, Understand Hangzhou and Shanghainese dialects
- Computer/IT: Type 130+ wpm, 97% accuracy

Proficient with Facebook, Twitter, Linkedin, Instagram, other social media, and major browsers. Able to navigate, compose simple web pages, repair laptop and phone screens, remove simple viruses

• **Software:** Proficient in Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Publisher, Outlook and Movie Maker, Audacity, WinRAR, beginner in Adobe Photoshop and PaintShop Pro

COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT/LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

Mobile Health at UGA: Mobile Technology Officer

Fall 2015-Spring 2017

- Repair and hardware evaluate cellular telephones to operational condition
- Plan and organize cellular telephone collection sites and programs

Institute of Electrical and Electronic Engineering: Treasurer/Fundraising Chair Spring 2015-Summer 2015

- Budget and fundraise hardware and software spending on competitions and robotics
- Manage and collaborate with sponsors and other important persons

Chinese Language Society - UGA: President

Summer 2014-Spring 2015

- Teach and expose the Chinese language and culture to non-natives
- Plan weekly events and major cultural awareness events (UGA's Lunar Festival)
- Connect Chinese language students with native Chinese speakers Program

Gentiva Hospice: Hospice Volunteer

January 2015-May 2015

• Plan fun activities with emotional support

WORK EXPERIENCE

Abercrombie and Fitch: Model/Sales Associate

March 2013-August 2015

- Engage customers with friendly service and helpful attitude
- Train new employees on procedures, product knowledge, and store policies

Thai Basil Sushi Zen: Hostess/Cashier/Packer

July 2008-June 2012

- Enhanced ability to multitask within a fast-paced environment (serve table, answer phone, pack order)
- Reconciled cash drawer at the end of each shift (organizing tips, finalizing transactions)

HONORS/AWARDS

State of Georgia Zell-Miller Scholarship Recipient	2012-Present
College of Public Health's Dean List Recipient	Fall 2015-Spring 2016
Athens Game Jam Hackathon First Place Recipient: Best Game Winner	April 3, 2016
CDC Principles of Prevention Certification	Fall 2015
UGA Academic Honesty Creative Contest First Place Winner: Original Video	May 2014